At the end of the 21st century, the Earth has been sick,
Contaminated and overpopulation.
Earth's richest residents to leave the planet
To preserve their lifestyle
Elysium
Max!
Come quickly.
Do not wait for the sisters.
It Frey.
He's also a new kid here.
You can read?
It's a giraffe.
He lived in Africa.
You can read?
Yes.
There are a lot of robot helpers there,
And they serve all day.
If you live there, you would not
Never been sick, or get old.
I'm going to take us there one day.
Really?
Yes, I promise.
Frey and Max.
Forever.
Max, what else did you steal?
You made me disappointed.
Why are you doing this?
So you can save money?
So you'll be able to buy tickets to go up there?
That place is not for you, or me.
But it's not fair, Sister.
Why should I not go there?
Sometimes there are some things that do not
Can be explained in life.
Why should all work properly.
But one thing I know.
You are something special.
Someday you're going to do
Something extraordinary.
Something that is destined for you.
My little Max.
Go to work, huh?
Beware not to burn.
Make this world so much better.
It's funny, I had no job.
I'll see you later.
Little friend, you think I have money?
What I seem to have money?
What about you, do you have any money?
Come on, what have you got in there?
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait.
Oh, it's 5 dollar.
Hey, wait a minute.
I had 5 dollars and I'm rich.
You know what that means?
So I can go to Elysium, huh?
All right.
Please immediately lined up.
Bus you've arrived.
I did not bring anything.
Do not touch me.
Clean.
Go on.
Good morning, Officer.
Detected criminals. Caught many times.
What's in your bag?
Hair Gel, mostly.
I'm just kidding.
Hey, hey .. I just want to work, man.
There is nothing in the bag.
Come on, I ...
Against the officer is an offense.
I just want to work, man.
Come on.
Clean.
I told you there's no nothing.
There is no tolerance and it also
Applicable to other citizens.
Really?
You must immediately report to
Parole officer.
Thank you, Citizen city.
No, thank you.
Frey, fractured two bones in the booth.
Max?
Frey ...
I thought you were ...
When did you come back?
It's a long time.
I see nothing has changed here.
No, it's not my fault.
Of course not. Let me see it.
How?
Broken really badly.
So you made it so a nurse, huh?
Yes.
That's good.
You still steal cars?
No, I did not do such a stupid thing again.
I worked in Armadyne.
I was on track, you know?
Frey, they need you on the 3rd floor.
I'll be right there.
So, you know, because you've come back ...
Wait a minute.
Just a minute.
Dominican, could replace me here?
Hey, listen, because you're back ...
Max, sorry I have to go.
Nice to meet you.
Stay away from the problem.
It is.
Listen ...
I know why you're gone,
I understand.
I just wanted to build
Go back a long relationship.
Dinner was with me.
I'll make coffee.
Not.
God.
I had to break my hand only
To get your attention?
Because I'll do it.
Stop it.
My life is complicated, Max.
I'm just, I'm ...
I miss you.
Shift I finished at 8 Wednesday, ok?
Yes, all right.
Coffee.
Yes, coffee. Good.
Get out of here.
Hello.
Before we started,
I want to explain ...
Max da Costa, violation of code of conduct in 2219.
Today at the bus stop 34-B.
Yes, that's what I want to talk.
I think it's been a misunderstanding.
We will extend the exemption
Bersyaratmu eight months.
Wait, what? No, no,
I can explain what happened.
I'm just kidding.
And, uh. You know ...
Stop talking.
The police reported antisocial behavior.
With regret we have to extend
Parole period.
Increased heart rate is detected.
You take the pill?
Not!
Thank you, I want to explain that to happen ...
Stop talking. Analysis showed personality
78.3% likely to commit aggression ...
Attack with a deadly weapon,
Resisting arrest.
You want to talk to a human?
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
What is it satire or contempt?
Negative.
Insulting officials is a federal crime.
Understood.
Hey! Da Costa!
You're late for your shift.
Yes, I have a little problem ...
No, no. You can not
Work with it.'re Out.
No, no, I'm fine.
I can work.
It will be released today.
I'm fine.
Are you healthy?
Healthy!
Okay, I pay you half a day.
Yes, all right.
You're lucky for it.
No detectable weapons.
You may enter.
Hey, look, man. Guess he likes you.
Did he bring his own plane these days?
It looks good.
If we are not able to increase profits,
Investors are we going to lose confidence.
You think what I'm doing here, on Earth?
You think I'm happy to breathe the air?
No, of course, but ...
I did everything that could be done ...
To re-boost
This company profits.
The company that I built myself.
Now, excuse me. I do not want to talk
With you guys again. Thank you.
Closing the number 34.
Heating the number 34.
Burn ID in his hand.
Come on, come on, we do not have much time.
Three transporter we have prepared, Spider.
All right, show on the screen.
Code accepted.
Turn on the plane!
We need Guider!
Welcome.
Hello, ma'am.
Have a look-see his garden.
Of course, thank you.
Halo.
Madame Delacourt.
Hi, It's been great, yes.
Hello.
What's up? Kids go?
Yes, they were together Dominica.
I have a present for you.
Take it with your mother.
There, next to the couch.
Lady, you want to drink fresh?
Command: Cancel.
Security is breached.
The code was reported stolen plane.
Sorry to bother you, ma'am. We saw some
Unregistered aircraft is approaching.
Good afternoon, Defense Secretary Delacourt.
Unregistered aircraft approaching 3
Elysium airspace.
Actions 6 and 7 are no longer effective.
Attention, the approaching aircraft.
You are not allowed to enter the airspace of Elysium.
Dad!
It's all right.
We will be forced to take action.
You violated the airspace of Elysium.
Warning standard does not work.
15,000 miles and is getting closer.
What should we do, ma'am?
Activate Kruger.
Mom, according to the executive order 355
About the illegal assets on Earth ...
I give you power.
Yes, ma'am.
Agent 32, we send the package.
Welcome, Agent Kruger!
10,000 miles and closer.
Sending coordinates on assets.
Three target data.
Shoot them!
Green light, 21-B.
Green light.
The missile was gliding!
Oh, shit.
Two aircraft were destroyed.
The total casualties of 46 people.
Collisions in 5 ...
Last missile failed.
That's ridiculous!
Only one who survived.
Ma'am, the plane enters our atmosphere.
The plane was registered first has landed.
I want everyone who dropped
The plane was captured.
ID is accepted.
Scan.
Broken in some parts
Detected
The process of reconstruction began.
No!
32 arrested, 13 were killed,
And 2 remain at large again, Mom.
Reconstruction is completed.
You have violated immigration laws.
All passengers have been arrested illegally, ma'am.
Yes.
Send them to deportation,
Remove them from the habitat.
Minister Delacourt,
Please immediately report to the President Patel.
Please report to the President Patel.
What's up, man?
What happened?
A little trouble with the police.
Are you okay?
Yes, do not worry.
Max, I have to talk to you.
You know ...
Not!
What do you mean?
You have not even heard of
What I'm saying.
Well, let's say.
All right.
You know Doseta house on the hill?
Yes, there's a lot of weapons.
Yes, they have five cars.
It's new.
We will go three.
Tomorrow, at lunch.
At lunch?
That's the plan?
Oh my God.
You've got a better plan?
Yes, bring one person.
Go before sunrise,
Take two fastest cars ...
And burn battery more cars.
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
I have to do? Oh, come on.
Give me one year. One year alone.
I'm not going back to jail.
A year alone, come on!
Look at you, once you are a legend,
And now what?
The time was 5:50 am.
No weapon was found.
You may enter.
Closing the number 34.
The door is not functioning.
Hey, did you hold the queue.
No, the door jam!
What are you doing to the door jam?
No, I'm just trying resetnya me.
Let me see.
Held its base.
Yes, I try removing them.
Get inside.
No, I ...
Look, you get into it now ...
Or find someone else who will,
And you can go from here.
Come on, man.
No. That's the deal, okay?
Begin!
Come on everybody, fast work!
Shit.
No, no, no, stop!
No, no!
Hey!
Organic Network detected K-34.
Come on! Get lost!
It's too late!
Extraction!
Those who start fights, Sister.
I just wanted to stay there.
You see how beautiful Elysium of here?
Yes.
All right.
Now look how beautiful
We look from up there.
Save it.
Now it's yours.
So you'll never forget where you come from.
What happened?
You're exposed to lethal doses of radiation.
You will experience organ failure ...
In five days, you will die.
What happened?
Why did production stop?
He's exposure to radiation.
Do not breathe on me.
Shut your mouth.
I'm sorry, sir.
What skin to peel off?
I do not want to change his bed.
Get him out of there.
Yes, sir.
Well, thank you.
Mr.. Carlyle, your plane ready to go.
Please sign this
To receive treatment.
Miporol will be very helpful.
Your body will work fine until death.
Take one tablet after a meal.
Thank you for your ministry.
At 3 pm yesterday you shoot down two aircraft
And killed 46 civilians.
Mandatmu is clean up the
This stowaway quietly.
I really understand it.
And using this agent ...
Mr.. M. Kruger.
15 violations of human rights ...
Rape, kidnapping, torture.
The man was diagnosed to suffer
Serious psychological problems.
We've asked for is no longer
Using a field agent.
Tell me, President Patel.
Do you have children?
It's not me who is being questioned here.
So I assume you do not have.
Maybe, if you have children.
Then you will be to maintain
Sustainability of this habitat.
I understand, is not a wise way
To think and act like me.
I really understand it.
But when they get into your house ...
The house you build for your children.
And the son of your son ...
Not PR or campaign promises
That will keep them away.
But I do!
Enough is enough!
This is your last warning.
Again unauthorized use of assets,
Then you will be transferred to the Lotus.
And Kruger's agent stopped permanently.
Who agrees?
Good.
Effective immediately.
Renewing the core.
Agent M. Kruger
Dismissed
You want a beer?
You have been dismissed from the CCB.
Please return all weapons to the nearest embassy.
To hell with your political!
Fuck you!
Look at that ...
Max ...
Max!
What's the matter with you?
What happened?
Gosh, let me help you.
Come on.
Max, what happened?
I should not get into it.
Where to?
Oh my God.
I was exposed to a lethal dose.
The lethal dose.
Everything will be okay.
Let me help you.
You'll be fine, Max.
They gave Miporol.
They gave me Miporol.
I've only got five days!
I only had five days!
You have to drink it.
They can heal everything in Elysium.
I know.
I'm going to see Spider.
Max, Max!
Drink the medicine!
Good so!
To see Spider, you need money.
I'll give you all I've got,
But it will not be enough for a ticket.
He's going to give me a ticket.
Frey, you know we've done
Everything to help your daughter.
But I talk to leaders, and they are
Advised her to go home with you.
How could I work here
And leave it at home?
You know it can happen anytime, Dr. Faizel.
I know, if he spasmed again, of course
Must be brought here, of course.
But he can not continue here.
This is not Elysium.
We can not directly cure.
Max!
A long time ago, my brother!
How's the weather affect you?
I've come to ask you a favor.
What? I can not hear you. What?
I need a ticket. Upward there.
And ID.
Oh.
Yes, yes, of course.
Of course, you want to sit in the aisle or window?
Do not play games with me.
I'm serious.
Listen, I'll be back.
I'll come back and work for you.
Everything you want.
I'll pay it.
You know?
This is ...
Priceless.
It's priceless.
Well, let me ask you something.
You know how many idiots who come here
And tells the same crap?
There are kids who come here every day.
Max, if I were you.
I'm going to go from here, now ...
I was jailed for four years because of you,
You have to help me up there.
Please shoot me. I was exposed to deadly radiation
And perhaps you will also be exposed.
You're really dying?
I was actually dying.
Look at this.
Peace.
Lower the gun. Derive the gun!
Lower the gun! Get out of here!
Okay!
Listen, I'm looking for someone
To do the job for me.
But nobody here had the guts!
You said you were ready to do anything, right?
Max ...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
This is ...
My friends.
This could be your ticket up there.
Final work for me,
You can be your way up there.
What is this?
Get the fuck out of Elysium, okay?
A millionaire who fell to Earth
To do business ...
He's here for, whatever.
We have kidnapped him.
Fuck you!
Calm down.
You can do it.
As a tourist.
Forget about the clock, forget his wallet,
Forget it all.
This, you have to take.
Organic Information,
Straight from the head.
I'm talking about the bank code,
Password, the login data ...
Access billions.
All you have to do is plug it into his brain,
Download the data to your brain with this thing ...
And bring me.
It's crazy, Max, come on.
If you're looking for a doctor, I can
Give the place up there.
Plus snacks and drinks.
All you have to do is go into a house,
Use the machine, and you're cured.
Sandro who will perform the operation.
Do you know him?
Oh my God.
I'm fine.
Actually, you look weak.
And messed up once, so ...
You know, I have ...
It's crazy, let's get out of here,
Come on, listen to me.
What should I do?
I would tell them to put up ...
This is ...
Wear protective third generation.
It will be connected to the system of nerves,
And will make you as strong as the Droid (robot).
You're like a knife, right?
Let's get out of here, please.
I need 4 people in the team.
But I alone chose it.
I send teknisiku own.
Transmitting data from the brain to the brain ...
It's hard.
Okay, but I brought Julio, he can
Ticket up there, just like me.
Yes, of course.
Okay, I will explore the background.
Wait!
The person should John Carlyle.
Carlyle Armadyne the CEO?
That's him.
Minister Delacourt, Tn. Carlyle has arrived.
You're here to convince me to renew
Our Armadyne contract, right?
Decisive as usual.
Come with me.
I'm not interested in your little idea.
I'm interested in something more substantial.
Habitat is dying.
There is a political disease in it.
Tumors that must be removed.
You and your company,
It takes advantage of this crisis.
So ...
You are building Thorus.
Can you take over the server and
Putting the power of the new president?
Coup?
You're suggesting a coup?
Is that possible?
I can do the reboot sequence ...
Turning the whole system,
And at that point ...
You can coup President, yes.
And that's what you're gonna do.
And the contract will be safe for the next 200 years.
Defense against missile battery, Droid, everything
We need to maintain our independence.
Of course, all guaranteed by the ...
Your new president.
Go on, you have a job, Mr.. Carlyle.
This is the guy.
He's the guy?
This is it.
Sit down.
Good job, man.
Take your time.
Slow down.
We gave her ID first.
We started with his ID first,
Prepare.
It will be linked to your DNA.
You ready?
It'll be fun.
Hey, man.
Yo.
What is this pain?
Yes, it will hurt.
It's going to hurt like hell.
When we are done you will be a ninja, huh?
Mariana!
Hey, bone saws bring it here!
It's not going to kill me.
You'll be fine.
Not bad.
Max.
I'm here.
We can do this, right?
We can do this.
Yes.
Hey!
He's awake!
You did, huh?
Amazing.
You can still masturbate, right?
How is she?
He's ready for action.
What are you doing to me?
Give you a way out.
Restart the protocol.
The order is completed.
You want to secure this data?
Yes No
Yes
Options:
A. Disable
B. Deadly.
Deadly.
Ready to upload to the brain.
Hey!
What's up, man?
How does it feel to wear that?
It seems very tight.
Show me.
Hold this.
Easy to use.
Just wait.
The ammunition that exploded in the air.
Blow up the enemy ...
Any ammo you shoot him
Will explode in a radius of 5 meters.
And ...
The explosion hardest by this naughty boy.
Time to work.
Sir ...
Your plane is ready.
On the way.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
All right, here's how it works.
We did not move until the plane departed.
Shoot plane with explosives,
We're surrounded when his plane crashed.
Okay, understood.
Explosive activated.
Come on, everyone.
Here we go.
Are you nervous?
Not.
No?
I got shat in my pants.
I will not die.
Not.
Come on, come on, come on!
Acceleration supersonic speed within 15 seconds.
Come on, Come on, Come on!
Blow, 3, 2, 1 ...
There was an engine failure.
Mom, there are people Elysium on Earth
Being in danger.
Bring up the data now ...
The people are identified.
John Carlyle. N8321 ...
I see you, fucker.
I've got a problem here.
Kruger, you hear me?
Ah, Mrs. Delacourt.
I love to hear your voice.
There are people who are carrying
Sensitive data in the city now.
A group of thieves trying to hijack it.
The citizens of what?
That's a secret.
You can not call the agent is not active,
For confidential information, eh?
The government does not know about that, right?
I can do it at will, right?
Preparing for the collision.
Please remain calm.
You do not suffer an injury.
Oh, it's very calming.
With one condition, if I do this,
I re-enabled.
All right.
I reassign two anggotamu.
You guys are very secret agents of course.
They should already be in your position.
Send the data to me the mission.
Come on, fellows.
Get out of the car!
Droid, it looks like some sort of
Wheeler vehicles, with one ...
Two passengers ...
They were armed and I want them dead.
Droid!
Loss! Loss!
Unidentified, Max da Costa.
Federal prisoner number 6149C-557-A ...
Jam!
It is!
She recharge.
All right! We have passed!
Come on! I protect you!
Come on, Come on. Come on!
Do not move.
Come on!
There's another one!
Die, you bastard!
Do not shoot the target!
No, No!
He's been shot!
People are traumatized heavy heart.
Blood pressure decreases.
His head did not hit!
Just his chest!
That's good.
Hold his head.
I connect it.
Quick install.
Come on, come on!
Yes.
Successfully?
Yes, we synchronize.
You do not know what you're doing.
One minute to the target, sir.
Well, we just went through.
I'm going to move now.
It works.
It is a database, ma'am.
They are men download now.
My friends, we have guests.
I'm dead!
Come on, fellows. Hurry.
That's Raven.
It's the military.
Well, it's 97. ... We ride 98
Hurry up, they come.
Just a little more! Little longer!
99!
This is it!
Damn The data must be broken!
What is that, what does it mean?
I can not read the data.
Scrambled! I can not read the data.
What?
Come on, man! We have to go!
What do you mean encrypted?
Fuck you!
No, no! Try again! Let's try again!
Let me go I go.
Please. Please try again.
Fuck you!
Let's get out of here.
What are you doing, Sandro?
Let's get out of here!
Asshole!
Come on, Max!
Get out of there!
Come on!
We have to go!
Come on, Max! Come on!
Hey, boss. Someone ran.
That's what I mean!
Asshole!
Target is moving south.
To the southwest.
Come on, Max!
They're coming!
There's another one.
All right!
This is wrong!'s All wrong!
Use the weapon, sir.
You think you could go anywhere?
Asshole!
Son of a bitch!
No!
No, no!
Wake up!
Get up!
No!
One person survived and escaped, ma'am.
They get the data.
Repeat. They get the data.
As soon catch the target.
Do not destroy the brain.
Come on! There were vague, comrade!
People have lost a lot of blood
That cause heart attacks.
Time of death, 17:45.
Come on, where are you hiding?
What's that?
It looks like a set of hog, boss.
Fuck! Find him!
Let's go back to the crash site!
Check out what they left behind.
Understood.
Thank you.
Boss, I think you should see this.
This is data that is transferred
Between Carlyle and criminals.
So that's why he wants it.
There are key to the kingdom in his head.
Now you have to find it.
Launching a spy plane.
Network 13, 3 to 11.
I ordered a full sealing.
Give the order no-fly
To Los Angeles.
The whole L.A?
The killer is still out there.
Until we catch him,
No one should leave the city.
Signal disturbed.
What the hell ...?
Max.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
We can go home.
Am I better?
I'll take the car, okay?
I'll be right back.
Frey ...
Max!
Jeez, what happened to you?
Damn, I'm going to call the doctor.
No, No!
I can not go in there.
Max!
I can not get there ...
Max, listen, you need a doctor, okay?
They're looking for me.
They will kill me.
I'm here to find you.
Max!
I need your help.
You have to pass through the system to be able to care.
Help me.
I do not want to die.
Max, Max!
Stay conscious!
I want to see him.
Mama will help her, okay?
Try to sleep.
Do not sleep!
Come on!
Max, you can do it, come on!
No, turn around!
Max, Max, wait.
Thank you.
Who did this to you?
Do not know.
I was injured at work.
I can work, from the Spider so
I could go up there and be healed.
Everything is so chaotic,
And now I'm in trouble.
Mom?
Hey, honey, come here!
Who is this guy?
His name is Max. Mothers know
When he was your age.
It's Mathilda.
Hi.
Go watch cartoons, okay?
I'll be right there.
I do not know you ...
Sorry, I must go.
Wait, Max, you can not go.
I should not have come here. I have to go!
Max! Him dying.
He was suffering from end-stage leukemia.
I told you my life complicated.
I need you to help me.
I do not know how to do this ...
Did what?
Brought to Elysium.
I can not help him.
I'll do it if I could.
How about this? Fake ID.
If you take us there,
What he can be cured with this?
That's not how it works.
It's coded for me,
And connected with my DNA.
People are looking for this, they ...
You do not understand who these people are.
If they find me here,
They will kill us all.
The only way I can
Help is gone., I promise.
He's all I have.
I'm sorry.
You bandaged.
Yes. Bandaged me.
What are you doing?
I do not want you hurt.
Want to hear a story?
No, ah ...
There's a meerkat who live in the forest.
He was hungry and his size.
Very little.
And the only large animals that could eat,
Because they can reach the fruit-buahannya.
So he's friends with a hippo ...
Okay, stop.
It will not end well for the meerkat.
Yes, because he was standing in the back of a hippopotamus.
To take all the fruit he wants.
What's in it for the hippo?
The hippopotamus needed a friend.
I'm sorry.
Possible targets.
Hey, boss.
We found him.
Landed the plane!
Mom, what's all okay?
All fine, dear.
Safe.
It's okay, sweetheart.
Good afternoon.
I'm sorry we came suddenly to the house,
Did not mean to scare your little princess.
I and my friends this,
Looking for a man ...
That was probably here.
I wish you could tell us
Where he was hiding.
Not.
I ...
I do not know where he is.
I do not believe it.
I hate violence
In front of the kids ...
So I want you to close your eyes, dear.
All fine, honey.
I want you to tell me.
It is remembered now?
Mama ...
Close your eyes, keep your eyes closed.
Close your eyes.
Please, I do not know where he is.
He's hurt, I help him and he's gone.
Help!
You know, people say now
Loyalty is hard to find.
What is this?
What do you build a hospital here?
He's sick.
He's sick? Let me see it.
It's nothing.
Do not touch him.
Did you see it? Instinct to protect.
I said do not touch him!
I just want to see your son.
Do not touch him!
Bring him. Come on!
Where are you taking him?
Unfortunately, all is fine.
All fine, honey.
Everything is fine.
Sit! Shut up!
Stop!
No, no, do not shoot him!
Lower the gun! Leave her alone!
You've got something, right?
What?
That's why they shut down
The whole sky, Come on, what's up?
Remittances, corporate data,
There must be something important in there!
Nothing. I did not get anything!
Everything is encrypted. Julio dead,
You owe me. Let's go now!
You can not be blocked flight system!
Nobody can go up there.
Until when?
Until I do not know.
I have to go there, I had to go up there.
All people want to go up there.
My people are working on it.
I'm thinking maybe the system
Can never be online again.
But, for now ...
Let us see what you have in mind.
Do not touch me!
Look at me, if they shut up the heavens,
For what's in your head ...
Perhaps the key to open it
Is also in there, is not it?
Come on.
Well ...
They'll hunt up
To the end of the world for this.
What's that?
It is a program reboot
Revive) for Elysium.
Anyone who has this, would have the power
To take over their entire system.
Opening the border ...
Making everyone so residents Elysium.
This could save your life.
We can save everyone.
When can I go?
They are trying to hijack the signal
Are blocked, but soon ...
Bullshit, when can we go?
I do not know.
Five days.
Fuck you, I do not have 5 days.
I only have a few hours ...
My people are working on it.
You always do,
You can not take me there.
I do not know why you continue to send people
Up there, they'll just fired.
Not with what's in your head!
That's what I mean!
We will control the system.
We can lead.
We can change history!
Wait a minute ...
What's in the head,
It means a lot to them, right?
Do not do this. If it falls into the hands
Wrong, they will kill us all.
Listen.
I'm going up there now.
If you find me, and I'm healed,
Then you can have all of this.
But I'm not going to die.
This is wrong, Max, do not do this.
Do not shoot him! Do not shoot him!
Do not shoot him!
It's nothing.
Everything is fine.
I always wanted to have a wife.
Never get married, you know?
Too much temptation.
But you ...
You made me ready to get married.
You made me ready to get married, darling.
Damn, sir.
Eh?
You'd better see this.
What? There's what?
Look at these fools.
Bring us back.
Drakey?
Yes, sir.
Open the door.
Stop right there and do everything I say.
Or I'll blow my head, understand?
Yes.
You can get everything in my head!
Just take me up there,
And take me to the medical capsule.
What I have is very valuable.
We can treat you.
Memasukanmu to medical capsule,
Something like that.
Let's go!
We will take you up there.
The air up there nice and clean.
Try it you'll like it.
Do not you dare!
Let's ride!
Come meet my friends, come on!
Do not be shy, I do not bite.
Introducing, the Drakey.
This is Max.
How are you?
Let's go!
Yes, ma'am, we've found the subject.
Open sky, we'll be there.
Will be waiting for you in 19 minutes.
Cancel fly.
Well, ma'am.
What's that?
What is it? We are connected again?
Marcelo What's happening? We're back?
We're back online, Spider.
Frey ...
I'm sorry ... I will
Fix everything.
We get it.
Okay. Where is he?
He left the Earth ...
He's heading Elysium.
Manuel! Rico! Prepare the weapon!
We're up.
Echo Leader 234, ask for permission
Land in sector 22.
Understandably Echo Leader 234.
You're allowed to enter.
I see you holding the G-1 there.
Hey, back off! Back off!
Or what?
I'll take it off.
Will you do it? Huh?
I want to have in your head.
Catch her!
Look out!
What should we do, ma'am?
I want all the people who came out of
The plane was captured by Homeland Security.
Evacuate everyone from level five
Out of the building, now.
I remind you about this.
The plane was registered just fell
Thorus and potentially harmful.
All because of your incompetence to act.
Evacuation him.
Put your hands on me.
It is a war situation.
It makes CCB is under my control.
Now, if you'll let me do my job.
I'm sure there is a fund raising event
You have to attend.
Come on, sir.
Max!
Get me out of here, Max!
I tried!
Air quality is down to a toxic level.
Get me out of here!
It is recommended that out of the plane immediately.
Run!
Asshole!
Two illegal residents heading north,
East location falls.
You killed two people,
I'll handle him.
Welcome to the spectacular property ...
Error.
No!
People go undetected.
He is sick, please help us, he's comatose.
Help!
He's awake.
You can let go of this thing?
Can not.
He connected with the data.
The data is bound to the nervous system.
The data are still intact, right?
The data seems to be intact.
If we take this data from it,
It will kill him.
It's nothing.
How long until you can download it
And turn on the system?
Not long, ma'am.
Keep everything remains confidential.
Lock all access.
Preparing now.
Remove them both from here.
Received.
Crowe, you want to bring the cheek boss?
Yes, be ready.
Warning.
One never registered aircraft approaching.
Bring him around in circles.
Make them busy.
Can.
Come on!
All right. 50 Hexabit, comrade.
You ready?
What are you doing to him?
Hey, What are you doing to him?
What will happen to him?
Hey!
Get up.
Wake up.
Max.
Max. Max.
Max!
Get in there!
The boss is really messed up, eh?
Hey, he's hit by a grenade.
She's fine.
But he will be very angry when they realized later.
Remember when he lost his leg?
Reconstruction of the face.
Kruger.
Boss?
It Crowe.
Where is he?
All right, all ready.
Let's get the data.
Take the needle! Take the needle!
Take the needle now!
Where they bring the girls?
Google.
Where is it?
Third floor.
Poison deadly radiation is detected.
You need medical care right away.
You're an idiot!
You realize what you're doing?
You dropped the vehicle is not licensed
To the inhabited area.
Your orders are to keep
This all remains a secret.
Do you remember what that means?
Are you crazy?
You're no use to me.
The administration realized what we were doing.
They'll hang us for treason.
For God's sake, Kruger!
Are you listening?
Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm listening.
Sorry, since we dropped the plane
And damaging the home page.
But nobody will hang
We as treason.
It is we who will hang them.
Lift your head and hold your wound.
It's not too powerful now, eh?
Get ready, man.
Elysium will soon have a decent president.
She needs treatment.
I was going to heal your daughter.
But now, I'll make sure he is
Would never heal.
Drakey, Do not believe all politicians.
Killing them all!
Thank you, boss.
I'll find you, little bastard.
And I'll take what should be mine.
This place is mine now.
You want to come and play with me?
Let's play.
Hey!
What the fuck is that?
All members of the CCB ...
Fast! Faster!
Come on! Come on!
Not.
No thanks.
People die.
Spider!
You heard me, Spider?
Max, where are you?
The data I have is, can make
All become citizens of Elysium, right?
Yes.
You know how to remove it, right?
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Okay, listen, and be careful.
Armament selected.
Ready.
Light.
All right.
Crowe, kill them both.
With pleasure, Boss.
With pleasure.
Where are you, an amateur?
Where are you?
How is it, sweetie?
Let's play.
Come on, I'll slow down, promise.
No. Do not please.
Come on.
Let go of me.
Are you ready? Come here.
No, please.
Asshole!
He's still alive?
For now.
Stay behind me.
I'll get you out of here.
I have a plan.
Did you hear that noise?
It's come to my voice!
I'll find you!
I'll be looking for you!
Well, Frey, we should split up.
What?
Listen.
You have to go upstairs,
Take this. Okay?
Find a home, find a medical capsule.
Max, it's not going to work.
Do not stop. Do not stop ...
He had no ID.
That's not going to work.
It would work this time.
I know how to fix it.
Surface is selected.
Go on.
Come with me.
I'm right behind you.
Not.
I promise.
Okay, a mother and her child
Just walked into the elevator.
They're up for a medical capsule.
Ask one of your men to
Make sure they get there.
And kutepati my promise.
Jump to a medical capsule.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
This way.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Almost there.
Go ahead!
That's what I meant.
To the door!
To the Door!
Fast! Faster!
Come on! Come on!
Come on, hurry.
Damn door. Come on!
Come on, you go first, let's go!
Emergency Locking is done ...
Come on!
Come on! Stand up!
Stand up! Stand up!
Come on!
You little bastard.
I will pluck your head.
No!
You have to stand up now.
Stay there.
Asshole!
Do you think it could be passed?
Come on, Max! Come on!
I'm just warming up.
Come on.
Get up now.
Stand up, come on!
Come on, I'm hurt, huh?
A little dizzy, huh?
What I'm about you?
Or are you bleeding?
Look at that.
I remind you.
You want to heal that little girl?
You just have to go through.
What was that, basic sissy?
You have to die.
We die together, kid.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, man, let's do it.
Come on!
Ready? Come on.
Call the guards, now!
Come on.
All right.
Let's do it.
Sorry.
The population of the Earth: ILLEGAL.
The population of the Earth: LEGAL.
Okay, we are ready, we are ready.
We're ready.
What?
Downloading the data would cause
Death to the data carrier.
Max.
It's nothing.
I know.
There's no way back from here.
There is no medical capsules can cure you.
All right, give it to me.
Take it.
Ready?
You just have to push that button.
Frey?
Max?
Max where are you?
I have to break my promise.
I can not go up there.
Remember what I said when we were young?
Yes.
One day I'll get us there.
Really?
Yes, I promise.
You will not believe what
I see now.
And tell Mathilda I love the story.
Really.
I understand why the Hippo
Want to do.
Come on!
You go first. Come on!
Every person has the privilege, Max.
Something that was destined for him.
What he got when he was born.
Restarting the system &gt;&gt;&gt; 5, 4, ...
Stop her!
Fuck you!
Let go of me!
Core renewed.
Residents Added new &gt;&gt;&gt;
Come on, please.
Residents
M. Santiago
Women
Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia
Detected
Back off, Officer.
Hold him!
I can not help citizens Elysium.
What?
Good work.
Guess Whose Elysium now.
New residents who need medical care.
Calculating ...
Launch of medical aid to the Earth plane.
You see how beautiful Elysium of here?
Now look how beautiful
We look from up there.
Now it's yours.
So you'll never forget where you come from.
My little Max.
Indonesian Subtitle by:
Geraldine